[theme music playing]
[Claire] You've done a number of
unspeakable things in the past,
and I never said anything about it.
But to have another woman raped?
That's unacceptable.
[Julio] Don't treat Miss Aguas
like Raul's mistresses
that you can easily get rid of.
If Arnaldo finds out about what you did,
your son won't be able to forgive you.
[Ivy] Even if you don't tell me
who's behind this,
-I know you work for Emilia!
-[gunshots]
Tell Emilia…
-[Diego] Let's go!
-I'm not afraid of her!
[Diego] Ivy, I want you to be happy.
I want you to be free from this burden.
You know how much I love you, right?
[Ivy] Diego, I love you.
[Arnaldo] I won't file for that
damn candidacy until I find Ivy.
You know, that woman's
trying to brainwash you.
Ivy isn't the problem. You are!
Because I despise that woman.
You know, I'm like a mad dog
dying to shred her into pieces
every time I see her!
[Ivy] I'm here to show you that
I am very much alive and well.
[Arnaldo] Let go! Let go!
What the hell is wrong with you two?
[Ivy] She sent her men to try and rape me!
[Nimfa] I know
where Camia's funds are hidden.
They came from an anonymous donor.
[Emilia] Okay, just make sure
you keep your promise
before I keep mine.
[Arnaldo] She will not get away with this.
Get away from me.
-What's wrong?
-Get away, Arnaldo!
-What's with you?!
-Get away!
[Arnaldo] Given you're in shock,
I will go the extra mile
to understand you. Rest for tonight,
so you can come with me
when I file for candidacy.
[suspenseful music playing]
-Guard.
-Sir?
-Good evening.
-Good evening, sir.
Where can I find the Serendipity Room?
I think you're looking for
the Serenity Room, sir.
It's over there.
You're Diego Torillo, right?
The one running for governor?
Yes, that's me.
Whatever you're up to, please
don't push through with it.
I know you're here
to investigate the Ardientes.
You don't know what
that family's capable of.
I can take care of myself.
Not everyone is as brave as you, sir.
If you push through with your plans,
I'll get in trouble for sure.
So, please just leave, sir.
[tense music playing]
[grunts]
-Is that all there is?
-Congressman…
we don't have enough men.
That's why business is slow.
Last I heard, our men
are now working for Jaguar.
That Jaguar sure is testing my patience.
[Domingo] Congressman,
should I make arrangements
for your meeting?
[chuckles]
Let me ask you, Domingo.
If you find yourself
in the middle of battle,
and you see your troops
switching their allegiance,
will you talk to your enemy?
-[Domingo] No, Congressman.
-That answers your question.
Talking to your enemy…
is tantamount to declaring surrender.
I must admit…
Jaguar has affected our operations.
But this isn't my only source
of livelihood.
I still have a lot of money.
I have lots of it.
I am not Julio Ardiente for nothing!
Now, as for Jaguar…
He's the one who's insignificant.
He's nothing but a cheap gangster
with a cheesy name.
For now…
let's allow him to think
he's winning the battle.
But at the proper time,
I'll show that Jaguar…
who the real king of this jungle is.
[dramatic music playing]
[Marlon] Everyone, thank you
for your time.
Now, I ask you to help
prepare the materials
for Diego's filing of candidacy tomorrow.
All of Diego's supporters need
to be there tomorrow,
so we can show the Ardientes
how big our group is!
-That's right!
-[woman] That's right!
We are doing this for Diego Torillo!
And we're doing this for the new Ardiente!
[Camia] Yes!
Diego Torillo for the new Ardiente!
[all] Diego Torillo for the new Ardiente!
-[Marlon] Thank you!
-[applause]
Get some rest, because you need
to look your best tomorrow.
I'm sure the ladies will want
to take selfies with you.
And try flirting with them too.
Batch, you're at it again.
I remember you were
a ladies' man in college.
[Marlon laughs]
[Marlon] Bro, charm trumps
intelligence every time.
Why do you think the Ardientes
are still in power?
And whether you admit it or not,
your grandfather
and your brother are very charismatic.
That's why they're still
in power. You'll need that.
Batch, if your heart sincerely
wants to serve the people,
you don't need to pretend
to be someone you're not.
[tense music playing]
-[Marlon] All right, bro!
-Take care. Thank you so much.
-Remember to vote for him, okay?
-Tomorrow.
-Yes.
-Are you all right?
Don't listen to him too much, okay?
You heard him.
I'm no good at teaching stuff.
-Are you guys all right?
-[woman] He's so handsome.
-[Marlon] He's Chris.
-[man] Okay.
-[Marlon] Okay.
-[Camia] That looks okay.
-[man] Fix those.
-[Marlon] Okay.
[applause]
[Marlon] Take care of them.
Okay. Very good!
Auntie, are you all right?
[woman] Yes.
-What's up, Mike?
-Everything's set, Diego.
-Yes, Diego, we're all set.
-Are we ready for tomorrow?
We're ready.
-You sure?
-We can do this!
[man] Of course!
Mayor, you need to sign
this for the campaign.
-Do you have the other one?
-Yes, everything's here.
-[Diego] What's up?
-[Mike] Diego!
-Mike, are you all right?
-[man] You're going to win!
-Aunt Camia.
-You're a man of the people.
-Nimfa.
-[indistinct chatter]
Are you ready for tomorrow?
[Pandoy] We'll do everything
to make those Ardientes lose.
-[Arnaldo] Is that it?
-[man] Yes.
Fix that up. I don't like that. Change it.
[Arnaldo] Fans and hats?
We need more of these.
[Diego] Here, let's roll these up.
-Let me help you.
-[man] Please roll those up.
[Camia] Let's tidy these up
so we can get some rest.
-Let's roll it up.
-No. I can do it, Nimfa.
[tense music playing]
[unintelligible]
-[Camia] There we go.
-All set.
ARNALDO: A TRUE ARDIENTE,
A MAN OF GENUINE COMPASSION
[Arnaldo] I want a bigger tarpaulin.
Print something bigger than this.
-[man] We need a bigger tarp.
-Okay?
[man] Is this the largest size?
The mayor wants something bigger.
All right.
-[Diego] Here.
-[man] We're ready for tomorrow.
[indistinct chatter]
We don't have something to tie it with.
-Batch.
-Where's the…
-[Diego] You're at it again.
I'll just help them.
[indistinct chatter]
There it is!
He's just going to bother you.
-[sensual music playing]
-[Emilia moans]
-Raul. What are you doing?
-Yes?
What?
What are you doing?
Nothing. I just know that
you've been exhausted lately,
from all the campaigning for your son.
Then there's Ivy Aguas…
who's been giving you nothing but stress.
Plus there's Papa.
He didn't give us his blessing
to renew our vows.
But… I vow to love you,
until the end of time, Emilia.
Oh.
I love you too.
Breakfast in bed?
-What?
-Here. I prepared it for you.
[sighs]
I made that.
[Raul chuckles]
-[giggles] This is too much.
-What? You don't want to eat?
No. But that's really sweet of you.
But are you happy?
It doesn't look like it.
It seems like you want
to eat something else.
[both laughing]
Well, I would love to. But…
-we have a long day today.
-Okay. What?
We have a lot to do today.
-[Emilia] Right?
-[Raul] And so?
[Emilia moans]
[tense music playing]
[laughs]
Why are your fingers so dirty?
-You should cut your nails.
-Is this dirty?
Ew!
Come on. It's just dirt.
Oh.
Let's eat.
-[laughs]
-Okay?
[ominous music playing]
[groans]
[screams]
[groaning]
Help!
Get them off me!
[screams] Help!
Grandpa? Grandpa?!
-That was Papa!
-Wait.
[coughing]
-Grandpa!
-Ouch! Ouch!
Grandpa, get up.
[both groaning]
Arnaldo, call the guards!
How did that get in here?!
Papa! What's happening?!
Oh, my! What's this mess?!
[Julio] Call all our guards!
Who brought that in here?! Tell me!
-Ouch!
-[Emilia screams]
-What's happening, Papa?
-It hurts! It hurts! It hurts!
[Arnaldo] I think you need
to take a shower.
[Emilia] Get rid of those!
[dramatic music playing]
[pensive music playing]
ARDIENTE BROTHERS TO FILE CANDIDACY
[phone ringing]
-Mom?
-[Camia sighs]
I can't believe that Emilia!
Diego told me what she did.
I want to see you.
Calm down, Mom.
We'll get our chance
to expose Emilia's true colors,
but you have to calm down.
When you see her later,
she can't suspect that you know anything.
I know that, Lily.
Is Arnaldo filing his candidacy later too?
Yes, Mom. It's complicated.
Maybe we should meet up.
You know the drill.
Be safe, Mom.
I will, dear. Especially now.
[tense music playing]
[Camia] Nimfa, I'm going
to the cooperative, okay?
I'll see you later.
Do you want me to go
with you now, Miss Camia?
I have nowhere else to be, anyway.
No, thanks. I'll be fine.
Besides, I have my bodyguards with me.
How do you plan on going to the rally?
[chuckles] You don't have
to worry about me.
I'll figure it out.
I'm sure I won't get lost.
I'm from around here, after all.
But, you should take care, Miss Camia.
It seems like the Ardientes
have it out for you.
-I'll see you later.
-Take care!
[foreboding music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[groans]
Uh… Wait here.
I just left something upstairs.
[suspenseful music playing]
[tense music plays]
[phone rings]
Mom?
[Camia] Lily.
I can't meet you today.
-Why not?
-It's Nimfa…
She's going through my things.
I need to deal with this first.
She's doing what?
[tense music playing]
Nimfa!
-What are you doing?!
-[quietly] Miss Camia…
[dramatic music playing]
I've noticed just how nosy
you can be, Nimfa.
But how can you go through my things?!
[sighs] This is unforgivable, Nimfa!
Please forgive me, Miss Camia. [gasps]
I won't do it again!
I have a confession to make.
Please hear me out.
I just really need some money.
My father is sick.
That's why he isn't here.
Because he needs treatment.
Please forgive me, Miss Camia!
[sobbing]
Nimfa, why didn't you tell me this before?
I could've helped you.
You shouldn't have done this.
But you've already done so much for me.
I couldn't dare ask any more from you.
Dad needs to undergo an operation.
We need a huge amount of money.
I didn't know what else to do, Miss Camia.
I'll help you.
I'll give you money.
But what you did was wrong.
And I don't know…
if I can still trust you after this.
Miss Camia, I'm begging you!
Please don't fire me.
I really need this job.
This is my only source of income.
I've got no job other than this.
I'm begging you!
This is my only hope.
I didn't know what to do, Miss Camia.
I'm sorry, Miss Camia. I really am.
Please forgive me.
I'm so sorry.
[sobbing]
What?!
Camia caught me.
I need to be extra careful.
I'm going to lie low for now.
My goodness! What about
the things you've always wanted?
The money, the jewelry, and the car?
What? Do you want to be
poor all your life?
Ma'am, calm down.
[Emilia] How can I calm down…
now that Camia knows
you've been spying on her?
So how are we going to prove
that she's connected to Ivy Aguas?
[sighs] Okay. Never mind.
Keep it low-key.
This is what you're going to do.
Since Diego will file for candidacy soon…
I want you to sneak in
and sabotage it, okay?
-I want to cripple them all.
-Hold on, ma'am.
That wasn't part of our agreement.
I only agreed to spy on them.
[chuckles] How about you give me
some incentives?
Do your task first.
Then, I'll give you a down payment.
[chuckles]
Yes!
You'll be surprised, ma'am.
I can say that it'll be a blast.
Make sure of that.
[tense music playing]
-[Emilia] Papa.
-Ouch!
You're welcome to stay here
in our room first,
while the maids clean up your room.
Stay here.
Never mind. Doctor. Don't worry about it.
It's nothing. I'm going to be fine.
These are just bites by these ants, okay?
You already prescribed
an ointment and some medicine,
I'll just take them.
You might have other patients
to attend to.
[sighs]
I will kill whoever did this to me.
I'm going to crush his larynx,
that he may never speak nor talk again!
What did the guards say?
[Raul] Um, nothing showed up
on the CCTV, Papa.
It was under maintenance.
Anyway, I asked the guards
to change all of the locks
here in the mansion.
And, Papa, I just want you
to know that I won't stop
until I find out who did this.
Okay. Okay.
[Emilia] I still can't believe it.
They had some nerve doing this!
They broke into the house
just to place those ants?
[Ivy] Hon?
Hon?
-[Arnaldo] Yes, hon?
-[Ivy] I received your text.
[Ivy] What happened?
-What is she doing here?
-Mom, please. Not now.
Oh, my. Congressman,
could this be an inside job?
[Raul scoffs]
That's possible.
What inside job? That's impossible!
Our employees are loyal to us, Ivy.
Why are you so defensive, Mr. Torillo?
Why are you saying that?
If you have nothing
good to say, just shut up.
[Arnaldo] Enough, Mom.
You have nothing to say--
[Emilia] Why don't you tell her that?
Hon, look.
[Arnaldo] You know, it won't hurt
to run a background check
on our employees.
Better yet, let's replace them all!
And while we're at it,
each and every one of us
should go through a background
check to find out the truth.
But why? We're all family here.
[laughs] No offense, but aside
from the three of us, Mom,
Grandpa, and I, we're
the only true Ardientes.
The rest are excess baggage.
[Raul] You better watch your mouth.
Or else what?
-What?
-[Julio] Stop it!
-Hon.
-[Julio] Shut up, all of you.
Please, please, please!
Raul, just listen to Arnaldo's
suggestion and check it out.
Do whatever needs to be done. Get it done!
Unless you have something to hide.
[chuckles]
[Julio sighs]
[dramatic music playing]
[Marlon] I think that's Miss Camia's car.
[man] It's Miss Camia. Miss Camia!
-[Marlon] She's here.
-[Pandoy] It's Diego.
[Marlon] Ma'am.
Let's go, Diego.
Are you ready?
Uncle, Nanny.
Anyway… Emilia.
Please get my suit ready
because we have to head
to that public appearance.
[Claire scoffs]
No, Papa.
You will just stay home.
It's just one event.
You can attend the others. Just rest.
She's right, Congressman.
It's better for you to rest.
Your condition might worsen
if you insist on going.
[Julio scoffs]
You and your short-sightedness.
You know what?
If I don't attend that event…
our enemies will think that we are weak!
Especially that Diego
and that blasted Jaguar!
They will start feeding on their delusions
and start thinking that,
yes, they have a chance
of beating the Ardientes!
But, anyway, thank you
for your concern, but no thanks.
I am going to that affair.
-Congressman.
-Grandpa!
-I told you, Papa.
-Oh, my!
Just rest.
-What happened?
-So stubborn.
Just rest, Papa. Okay?
-[Claire] Lay down.
-Congressman, please.
I'm asking you. Let us handle it.
Okay? We'll go there on your behalf.
Exactly. We'll make you proud, Papa.
[Julio] Okay, fine. Go. You better.
[pensive music playing]
[Marlon] Everyone, to give
us all a special message,
here's our future governor, Diego Torillo.
[Diego's supporters]
Diego, Diego! Diego, Diego!
Diego, Diego!
Friends…
the day we dreamed of has finally arrived.
It's time to file for my candidacy
as the governor of Poblacion Ardiente.
[Diego's supporters]
Diego, Diego! Diego, Diego!
Diego, Diego! Diego…
[Diego] Now's the time
we've all been waiting for!
It's time for us to see the ray of hope
that will put an end
to the dark and corrupt
governance here in Ardiente!
[Arnaldo's supporters] Viva Ardiente!
I will fight for justice!
Viva Ardiente! Viva Ardiente!
-[Marlon] Diego, they're here.
-Diego, Diego! Diego, Diego!
Diego, Diego! Diego, Diego!
Diego, Diego! Diego, Diego! Diego, Diego!
-Viva Ardiente! Viva Ardiente!
-Diego, Diego! Diego, Diego!
-Viva Ardiente!
-Diego, Diego! Diego…
My friends, thank you for coming here
to show your support.
Now, let me hear your loud cheer
for Arnaldo Ardiente-Torillo,
the righteous servant
of Poblacion Ardiente!
Viva Ardiente!
Viva Ardiente! Viva Ardiente!
I'm Diego Torillo,
your true friend
and ally for a new Ardiente!
Diego, Diego! Diego, Diego! Diego, Diego!
Diego, Diego!
I'm Arnaldo Ardiente-Torillo,
your righteous servant!
Viva Ardiente!
Viva Ardiente! Viva Ardiente!
The Ardientes?
You're nothing but devious
and greedy criminals!
Let's bring down the Ardientes!
Don't vote for the Ardientes!
-[booing]
-[indistinct chatter]
Camia, Camia, Camia.
Wait, I don't even think I need this.
Did you know that it's not right
to bad-mouth
your political rival?
That's below the belt. Big no-no!
And you even have the guts to lecture me
about attacking below the belt?
Hey, Emilia!
Look at yourself in the mirror.
You are the queen of hired killers
and hired rapists in this place!
Camia, wait. What do you know about me?
Do you have any proof
that I tried to have Ivy Aguas raped?
You know, you don't have common sense.
-Mom, that's enough.
-Wait!
I'm just telling the truth.
This woman doesn't have common sense.
Why would you even think
that Ivy would be supporting us
if she knew that I was the one
who tried to have her raped?
Ivy, come on. Speak up. Why are you here?
[tense music playing]
Of course, I'm only here
to support my Arnaldo.
See? She's a very supportive fiancée.
For all we know,
you might be the ones
who tried to have her raped,
then now, you put the blame on us?
You know, Emilia,
since the start
you've been such a good liar!
[moans]
-Thank you.
-You're welcome!
Do Camia and Diego actually believe…
they can take on the Ardientes?
How ambitious.
And they say there's
no more good TV nowadays.
But this is a really good show.
[chuckles]
Cortez.
Go find Raul.
Tell him I have a job for him.
Yes, Congressman.
[chuckles]
Let's go.
-[man] Viva Ardiente!
-Viva Ardiente! Viva Ardiente!
Viva Ardiente!
Viva Ardiente! Viva Ardiente!
-Viva Ardiente!
-Diego, Diego!
-Diego, Diego! Diego, Diego!
-Viva Ardiente! Viva Ardiente!
-Viva Ardiente!
-Diego, Diego! Diego, Diego!
[reporter] We're here today
to witness the filing of candidacy
of Arnaldo Ardiente-Torillo
and his half-brother,
Diego Ardiente-Torillo.
[ominous music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Emilia] Hello?
Didn't you tell me…
Diego's party wouldn't make it?
What are they doing here?
Don't worry, Mrs. Emilia.
I'm already working on it.
[sighs] Okay.
[suspenseful music playing]
[dramatic music]
-Diego, Diego! Diego, Diego!
-Ardiente!
I had no idea they would
be wearing green today.
And you didn't tell me
our color was maroon. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Ardiente! Ardiente!
Ardientes are the best!
[dramatic music playing]
Papa.
Raul, come here. Have a seat.
-[Julio clears throat]
-[Raul exhales]
Yes?
Raul, since all you'll be doing
during the filing
will be putting on a smile
and having your pictures taken,
I realized you're the perfect person
to help me with my little problem.
Thank you for considering me
and calling me here.
[clicks tongue] Of course, of course.
You know, I've come to the conclusion
that there are only
two suspects I can have,
who could possibly be responsible for…
[hisses]
…that fiasco that happened
earlier in my room.
[clears throat]
[Julio] Suspect number one. Diego.
Why? For obvious reasons.
When he was a kid, I let warrior
ants swarm all over him.
Now, he wants revenge.
And a good thing came out of it.
I mean, you've seen it.
If he's the culprit,
that means he grew some balls.
And now he's going against the Ardientes.
But, I don't think he's capable
of doing such…
a dastardly, sneaky act like that.
Which brings me to my second suspect…
Jaguar.
[dramatic music]
I don't know if he's daring
enough to break into my house.
Or if one of our security
personnel is betraying us.
That's why if it's okay with you,
I want you to investigate…
and, if possible,
annihilate this creature
who calls himself "Jaguar".
[tense music playing]
EVEN IF I'M BY THEIR SIDE,
YOU STILL HAVE MY SUPPORT.
[phone dings]
EVEN IF I'M BY THEIR SIDE,
YOU STILL HAVE MY SUPPORT.
-I'm sorry I'm late, Diego.
-Nimfa, what took you so long?
I was embarrassed
to show myself to Aunt Camia.
I thought she was still mad at me.
What? Why? What happened?
Diego, let's talk about it later.
[suspenseful music plays]
[line ringing]
Hello.
Rufo.
I'm going to your hideout.
Before I get there, you need to be gone.
Because Julio gave me an order.
He ordered me to annihilate
every one of you.
Jaguar… Relax.
We don't need to leave.
All we need to do
is prepare for their arrival.
-[clapping]
-[camera clicks]
[ominous music playing]
[camera clicks]
-I think it's our turn.
-Let's go, Diego. This is it.
It's official.
Your dream's about to come true.
Thank you, Uncle.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you very much.
-[Arnaldo] Let's go.
-[Loring] This is it.
[suspenseful music playing]
-[Pandoy and Loring laugh]
-Thank you. Thank you.
-[man] Mrs. Loring.
-What?
-I need to tell you something.
[man] Your house is burning.
-[Pandoy] What?
-[man] It's burning.
[man] Come on!
Diego, our house is burning down.
What? Marlon, you stay here.
I need to make sure nobody got hurt.
-[Marlon] Yes.
-Aunt Camia.
[Marlon] I'm sorry, but we have
to leave. Thanks again.
[tense music playing]
[Loring sobbing]
-Wait. [screams]
-Loring… What?
[Loring wailing]
[Pandoy] Loring…
[Pandoy] Loring, what about the funds?
-[Pandoy stammering]
-[Loring wailing]
-[Pandoy] Where'd you keep the--
-Pandoy… Pandoy.
[Loring] We lost all our money!
[Loring sobbing]
Diego…
Pandoy, this wasn't an accident.
They made it look like
the house caught fire,
but they took our money!
They took everything!
[wailing]
[Marlon] Diego…
All our campaign materials caught on fire.
They burned it all.
I know you're all devastated.
I'm devastated too.
It's hard to see
all our hard work turn to ash.
Marlon, schedule our meeting
with Senator Magno.
Okay, Diego. I'll take care of it.
[Loring sobbing]
Those bastards!
[dramatic music playing]
We'll get back at them. They'll pay.
[man] Boss, we're all set.
[suspenseful music playing]
[phone ringing]
Do it now.
All right.
[dramatic music]
[gunfire]
[loud explosion]
[tense music playing]
[dramatic music]
They planned it.
They knew we were busy
with the filing and rally,
so that's when they attacked our place.
They've always played dirty!
But, how did they know
where we hid our funds?
Don't you think they have a spy here?
[ominous music playing]
An ally of the Ardientes
who watches our every move.
[sighs]
Diego, I'm sorry.
I know she's your friend…
but I can't help
but be suspicious of Nimfa.
I caught her going through my things.
She said her father was sick,
and she badly needed money.
Are you saying Nimfa stole our funds?
[sighs]
I'm not sure, Diego.
It's just that with the turn of events,
I feel like something's off about her.
[suspenseful music playing]
Miss Camia. Are you suggesting I did this?
Nimfa.
You already gave me another chance,
and I won't throw it away.
I just did that because I was
really desperate then.
[crying]
[Diego] Nimfa…
You're my friend so I trust you.
But we can't trust the Ardientes.
We're just worried about you.
What if…
What if the Ardientes
really are using you?
I'm not their lapdog!
[scoffs] How could you
even think of that, Diego?
We've been friends for so long.
But it's fine if that's
what you think of me,
I'll just leave Miss Camia's place.
I don't want to lose your trust.
Nimfa… Don't say that.
I can't let you lose your job.
Because you have to help your father.
So, you don't have to quit.
[suspenseful music playing]
Thank you, Miss Camia.
I won't ever do that again.
I'll cut my hands myself
if I ever do it again.
I promise I will never break your trust.
Thank you.
[Emilia] Come, Aunt Claire.
You have to see this.
-[Claire] What is it?
-We have to check it out.
Okay.
Money.
Money again. Boring.
This, Aunt Claire…
Hmm… Check.
Through this, we will prove
if Ivy Aguas is Camia's backer.
[chuckles]
We can finally put an end
to Ivy Aguas' betrayal.
What can I say?
Good job, Emilia.
-Well thank you, Aunt Claire.
-[Claire chuckles]
-[Claire] Well done.
-So, what are we celebrating?
Well, aside from that thing with Diego,
I just got some information
that they're headed to Senator Magno,
so you have to set up an
appointment and beat them to it.
Okay, sure.
-[Ivy] Hon?
-Hon?
[Ivy] Oh, were you guys talking?
What was it about?
Oh. Sorry, Ivy.
It's strictly for family members
only, so we can't tell you.
Mom, Ivy's practically part
of the family already.
Part of the family?
Wow, how can that be
when she's accusing me
of being the mastermind of her rape?
Hon, let me.
Oh, Emilia, did you already
forget what I did earlier?
Didn't I put on an act with you
in front of a lot of people
even though you're blaming the other party
for something you yourself planned?
[exhales]
Okay, you know what? Let's stop this.
I'm doing this for Arnaldo, and…
besides, you're going to be
my mother-in-law.
I know we had some conflicts
these past few days, but…
I've had enough of this,
my future mother-in-law.
So, I was hoping
we could go back to being okay.
[sighs]
Thank you, mother-in-law.
Okay, we're good.
-Mamita.
-So, who apologized first?
Oh.
Future mother-in-law,
that's not important.
-Congressman.
-[Julio] Look at that.
Such a beautiful portrait.
Future mother-in-law
and daughter-in-law in each other's arms.
[Emilia and Ivy chuckling]
A while ago, they were
at each other's throats.
[Emilia] I know.
[Julio] Women are the hardest
creatures to understand.
Well, Papa, did you see
what happened to Diego today?
Oh, yes. And I'm so proud of all of you.
Seems like everybody's
in each other's arms
and waving peace signs at each other.
Maybe we can celebrate
as one family again?
That would be great, Papa.
Perfect timing
because I had dinner prepared.
Oh, good. I'm famished. Let's go?
[Emilia] Let's go.
Let's all have dinner together.
[phone rings]
[Emilia] What's for dinner?
Hello?
[Raul] Papa. Looks like Jaguar
got ahead of us.
Most of our men were killed.
-What?!
-Papa?
-Yes…
-[Emilia] What's going on?
I'll call you later. Nothing. [chuckles]
Just some shocking news I heard.
Everything's fine.
It's just that I left something
in the office.
I'll just go and get it. I'll be back.
Make sure you join us for dinner, Papa.
-Yeah, for sure.
-[Emilia] All right.
[Emilia] Help yourselves. Come
on. Sit down. Let's have dinner.
[Julio screams]
[screams]
You bastard! Jaguar, you bastard!
-Domingo! Get in here!
-[Domingo] Congressman.
I held back for far too long
from those bastards.
Find the families of all our former men
who betrayed us and sided with Jaguar.
Yes, Congressman.
It's time for me to teach them a lesson,
so they will know
the wrath of Julio Ardiente!
Go!
[groans]
[dramatic music playing]
[Ivy] There's a spy in Diego's camp?
We're a political family,
and we have been doing this
for many, many years.
[Emilia] I'm giving you until tonight
to finish your job.
Or else… Do you see that toilet?
That's the last thing
you'll see before you die,
you piece of shit!
[Camia] Lily, thanks for helping
out with Diego's campaign.
[Emilia] Do you have an update on Camia?
Lily Cruz is alive.
[theme music playing]